P/ANIMAL,P/CONTACT_INFO,P/CONTACT_INFO/url,P/DISEASE,P/EVENT,P/EVENT/HURRICANE,P/EVENT/WAR,P/FACILITY,P/FACILITY/AIRPORT,P/FACILITY/ATTRACTION,P/FACILITY/BRIDGE,P/FACILITY/BUILDING,P/FACILITY/HIGHWAY_STREET,P/GAME,P/GPE,P/GPE/CITY,P/GPE/COUNTRY,P/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE,P/LANGUAGE,P/LAW,P/LOCATION,P/LOCATION/CONTINENT,P/LOCATION/LAKE_SEA_OCEAN,P/LOCATION/REGION,P/LOCATION/RIVER,P/ORGANIZATION,P/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION,P/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL,P/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT,P/ORGANIZATION/HOSPITAL,P/ORGANIZATION/HOTEL,P/ORGANIZATION/MUSEUM,P/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL,P/ORGANIZATION/RELIGIOUS,P/PERSON,P/PLANT,P/PRODUCT,P/PRODUCT/VEHICLE,P/PRODUCT/WEAPON,P/SUBSTANCE,P/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL,P/SUBSTANCE/DRUG,P/SUBSTANCE/FOOD,P/WORK_OF_ART,P/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK,P/WORK_OF_ART/PLAY,P/WORK_OF_ART/SONG

_:nP/CONTACT_INFO/url,P/CONTACT_INFO
_:nP/EVENT/HURRICANE,P/EVENT
_:nP/EVENT/WAR,P/EVENT
_:nP/FACILITY/AIRPORT,P/FACILITY
_:nP/FACILITY/ATTRACTION,P/FACILITY
_:nP/FACILITY/BRIDGE,P/FACILITY
_:nP/FACILITY/BUILDING,P/FACILITY
_:nP/FACILITY/HIGHWAY_STREET,P/FACILITY
_:nP/GPE/CITY,P/GPE
_:nP/GPE/COUNTRY,P/GPE
_:nP/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE,P/GPE
_:nP/LOCATION/CONTINENT,P/LOCATION
_:nP/LOCATION/LAKE_SEA_OCEAN,P/LOCATION
_:nP/LOCATION/REGION,P/LOCATION
_:nP/LOCATION/RIVER,P/LOCATION
_:nP/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION,P/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL,P/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT,P/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/ORGANIZATION/HOSPITAL,P/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/ORGANIZATION/HOTEL,P/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/ORGANIZATION/MUSEUM,P/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL,P/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/ORGANIZATION/RELIGIOUS,P/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/PRODUCT/VEHICLE,P/PRODUCT
_:nP/PRODUCT/WEAPON,P/PRODUCT
_:nP/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL,P/SUBSTANCE
_:nP/SUBSTANCE/DRUG,P/SUBSTANCE
_:nP/SUBSTANCE/FOOD,P/SUBSTANCE
_:nP/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK,P/WORK_OF_ART
_:nP/WORK_OF_ART/PLAY,P/WORK_OF_ART
_:nP/WORK_OF_ART/SONG,P/WORK_OF_ART
_:nP/EVENT,nP/CONTACT_INFO
_:nP/LOCATION,nP/ANIMAL
_:nP/PRODUCT,nP/EVENT
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/EVENT
_:nP/CONTACT_INFO,nP/ANIMAL
_:nP/EVENT,nP/GPE
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/PRODUCT
_:nP/PERSON,nP/PLANT
_:nP/GPE,nP/LAW
_:nP/GPE,nP/GAME
_:nP/WORK_OF_ART,nP/GAME
_:nP/PRODUCT,nP/GAME
_:nP/GPE,nP/PLANT
_:nP/LAW,nP/FACILITY
_:nP/GPE,nP/EVENT
_:nP/EVENT,nP/GAME
_:nP/GAME,nP/LAW
_:nP/PRODUCT,nP/FACILITY
_:nP/GAME,nP/PRODUCT
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/SUBSTANCE
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/FACILITY
_:nP/PLANT,nP/FACILITY
_:nP/LOCATION,nP/PRODUCT
_:nP/GAME,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/LOCATION,nP/CONTACT_INFO
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/WORK_OF_ART
_:nP/LAW,nP/LOCATION
_:nP/WORK_OF_ART,nP/ANIMAL
_:nP/WORK_OF_ART,nP/LOCATION
_:nP/LOCATION,nP/PLANT
_:nP/ANIMAL,nP/GPE
_:nP/GAME,nP/SUBSTANCE
_:nP/WORK_OF_ART,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/GAME,nP/CONTACT_INFO
_:nP/ANIMAL,nP/LANGUAGE
_:nP/GAME,nP/ANIMAL
_:nP/EVENT,nP/ANIMAL
_:nP/PRODUCT,nP/WORK_OF_ART
_:nP/PERSON,nP/LANGUAGE
_:nP/LAW,nP/GAME
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/LANGUAGE
_:nP/ANIMAL,nP/PERSON
_:nP/PERSON,nP/ANIMAL
_:nP/FACILITY,nP/GAME
_:nP/FACILITY,nP/LAW
_:nP/LOCATION,nP/LAW
_:nP/CONTACT_INFO,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/GPE,nP/SUBSTANCE
_:nP/SUBSTANCE,nP/GPE
_:nP/ORGANIZATION,nP/LAW
_:nP/GAME,nP/PLANT
_:nP/ANIMAL,nP/LAW
_:nP/ORGANIZATION,nP/GAME
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/CONTACT_INFO
_:nP/FACILITY,nP/PRODUCT
_:nP/PERSON,nP/PRODUCT
_:nP/PRODUCT,nP/LANGUAGE
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/LOCATION
_:nP/SUBSTANCE,nP/GAME
_:nP/LAW,nP/WORK_OF_ART
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/EVENT,nP/PLANT
_:nP/FACILITY,nP/CONTACT_INFO
_:nP/FACILITY,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/WORK_OF_ART,nP/PRODUCT
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/PERSON
_:nP/ORGANIZATION,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/ORGANIZATION,nP/PLANT
_:nP/SUBSTANCE,nP/LANGUAGE
_:nP/ORGANIZATION,nP/ANIMAL
_:nP/LAW,nP/GPE
_:nP/CONTACT_INFO,nP/LANGUAGE
_:nP/PERSON,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/FACILITY,nP/ANIMAL
_:nP/GPE,nP/WORK_OF_ART
_:nP/SUBSTANCE,nP/LAW
_:nP/PRODUCT,nP/CONTACT_INFO
_:nP/FACILITY,nP/WORK_OF_ART
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/LAW
_:nP/ANIMAL,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/PLANT,nP/EVENT
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/GAME
_:nP/ANIMAL,nP/LOCATION
_:nP/GAME,nP/GPE
_:nP/LOCATION,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/EVENT
_:nP/PRODUCT,nP/GPE
_:nP/CONTACT_INFO,nP/GAME
_:nP/LAW,nP/PERSON
_:nP/PRODUCT,nP/PERSON
_:nP/LAW,nP/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/SUBSTANCE,nP/CONTACT_INFO
_:nP/GAME,nP/FACILITY
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/GPE
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/PERSON
_:nP/SUBSTANCE,nP/WORK_OF_ART
_:nP/GPE,nP/ANIMAL
_:nP/WORK_OF_ART,nP/SUBSTANCE
_:nP/CONTACT_INFO,nP/SUBSTANCE
_:nP/SUBSTANCE,nP/EVENT
_:nP/GPE,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/PLANT,nP/WORK_OF_ART
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/ANIMAL
_:nP/PRODUCT,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/PERSON,nP/LAW
_:nP/GAME,nP/LANGUAGE
_:nP/LAW,nP/ANIMAL
_:nP/ANIMAL,nP/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/GAME,nP/EVENT
_:nP/CONTACT_INFO,nP/LAW
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/GPE
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/LAW,nP/SUBSTANCE
_:nP/PERSON,nP/GAME
_:nP/GPE,nP/PRODUCT
_:nP/ANIMAL,nP/GAME
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/CONTACT_INFO
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/ANIMAL
_:nP/LOCATION,nP/SUBSTANCE
_:nP/PLANT,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/PLANT,nP/GAME
_:nP/SUBSTANCE,nP/LOCATION
_:nP/CONTACT_INFO,nP/FACILITY
_:nP/ANIMAL,nP/EVENT
_:nP/PLANT,nP/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/LAW,nP/PLANT
_:nP/ANIMAL,nP/WORK_OF_ART
_:nP/CONTACT_INFO,nP/EVENT
_:nP/LAW,nP/CONTACT_INFO
_:nP/PLANT,nP/LAW
_:nP/WORK_OF_ART,nP/GPE
_:nP/LAW,nP/LANGUAGE
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/PRODUCT
_:nP/EVENT,nP/PRODUCT
_:nP/FACILITY,nP/PLANT
_:nP/GAME,nP/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/WORK_OF_ART,nP/FACILITY
_:nP/CONTACT_INFO,nP/PRODUCT
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/GAME
_:nP/LAW,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/LOCATION,nP/WORK_OF_ART
_:nP/CONTACT_INFO,nP/LOCATION
_:nP/GAME,nP/WORK_OF_ART
_:nP/WORK_OF_ART,nP/LAW
_:nP/PRODUCT,nP/LOCATION
_:nP/ANIMAL,nP/FACILITY
_:nP/EVENT,nP/SUBSTANCE
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/FACILITY
_:nP/GPE,nP/CONTACT_INFO
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/ORGANIZATION
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/LAW
_:nP/CONTACT_INFO,nP/GPE
_:nP/EVENT,nP/LANGUAGE
_:nP/WORK_OF_ART,nP/PLANT
_:nP/PLANT,nP/LOCATION
_:nP/LOCATION,nP/LANGUAGE
_:nP/PLANT,nP/PERSON
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/LOCATION
_:nP/LAW,nP/PRODUCT
_:nP/ORGANIZATION,nP/LANGUAGE
_:nP/GAME,nP/LOCATION
_:nP/GAME,nP/PERSON
_:nP/PLANT,nP/GPE
_:nP/ANIMAL,nP/CONTACT_INFO
_:nP/PLANT,nP/LANGUAGE
_:nP/PLANT,nP/CONTACT_INFO
_:nP/EVENT,nP/DISEASE
_:nP/LOCATION,nP/GAME
_:nP/PRODUCT,nP/LAW
_:nP/FACILITY,nP/LANGUAGE
_:nP/LANGUAGE,nP/PLANT
_:nP/DISEASE,nP/PLANT
_:nP/CONTACT_INFO,nP/PLANT
_:nP/GPE,nP/LANGUAGE
_:P/ANIMAL,P/CONTACT_INFO,P/CONTACT_INFO/url,P/DISEASE,P/EVENT,P/EVENT/HURRICANE,P/EVENT/WAR,P/FACILITY,P/FACILITY/AIRPORT,P/FACILITY/ATTRACTION,P/FACILITY/BRIDGE,P/FACILITY/BUILDING,P/FACILITY/HIGHWAY_STREET,P/GAME,P/GPE,P/GPE/CITY,P/GPE/COUNTRY,P/GPE/STATE_PROVINCE,P/LANGUAGE,P/LAW,P/LOCATION,P/LOCATION/CONTINENT,P/LOCATION/LAKE_SEA_OCEAN,P/LOCATION/REGION,P/LOCATION/RIVER,P/ORGANIZATION,P/ORGANIZATION/CORPORATION,P/ORGANIZATION/EDUCATIONAL,P/ORGANIZATION/GOVERNMENT,P/ORGANIZATION/HOSPITAL,P/ORGANIZATION/HOTEL,P/ORGANIZATION/MUSEUM,P/ORGANIZATION/POLITICAL,P/ORGANIZATION/RELIGIOUS,P/PERSON,P/PLANT,P/PRODUCT,P/PRODUCT/VEHICLE,P/PRODUCT/WEAPON,P/SUBSTANCE,P/SUBSTANCE/CHEMICAL,P/SUBSTANCE/DRUG,P/SUBSTANCE/FOOD,P/WORK_OF_ART,P/WORK_OF_ART/BOOK,P/WORK_OF_ART/PLAY,P/WORK_OF_ART/SONG
